Taxi driver: Where to ma’am?
Eve: Hello.
To the airport, please.
Taxi driver: JFK or Newark?
Eve: JFK, please.
Oh dear.
The traffic is bad this morning.
Taxi driver: Yes. It’s terrible.
Where are you from?
Eve: I’m from Manchester but I live in London.
Are you from New York?
Taxi driver: No, ma’am, I’m from Puerto Rico.
Eve: Oh, do you like New York?
Taxi driver: It’s a great city, but it’s very expensive.
Eve: London is very expensive, too.
Do you have children?
Taxi driver: I have two daughters.
Eve: Oh really?
I have two sons and a daughter.
David and Andrew are at university, and Carla’s at school…
Taxi driver: OK. Here we are.
Eve: How much is that?
Taxi driver: That’s $87.50.
Eve: Oh. Here’s $100.
Keep the change.
Taxi driver: Thanks. Have a good flight!
Eve: I need to hurry. I’m late!
Announcement: This is the final call for flight BA641 to London Heathrow.
Would all passengers please proceed to gate B5?